<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>event on Liam Getreu</title>
    <link>https://liamgetreu.com/tags/event/</link>
    <description>Recent content in event on Liam Getreu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-au</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://liamgetreu.com/tags/event/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NIF event: In conversation with Senator Penny Wong</title>
      <link>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/penny-wong-10-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/penny-wong-10-years/</guid>
      <description>For the event celebrating 10 years since the New Israel Fund&amp;rsquo;s establishment in Australia we hosted a number of speakers, including Senator the Hon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIF event: Foreign Correspondents Speak Out</title>
      <link>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/foreign-correspondents-nif-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/foreign-correspondents-nif-event/</guid>
      <description>For this NIF event, I moderated a discussion with John Lyons, the author of a new book, Dateline Jerusalem which looks at how Israel is covered by the Australian media and a former Middle East Correspondent for the Australian, Anshel Pfeffer senior correspondent and columnist for Haaretz and the Israeli correspondent for the Economist and Dina Kraft, a Tel Aviv-based journalist for the Los Angeles Times and Christian Science Monitor, to hear how foreign correspondents work to tell other people’s stories and shape the discourse in their home country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIF event: What the Biden-Harris Administration Means for the Middle East</title>
      <link>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/biden-harris-foreign-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/biden-harris-foreign-policy/</guid>
      <description>Less than two weeks after President Joe Biden took office, I interviewed seasoned American Middle East negotiator, and NIF board member, Aaron David Miller and former Knesset member Ksenia Svetlova about how America’s Middle East policy will shift under the new administration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIF event: Democracy in Danger</title>
      <link>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/democracy-in-danger-trump-biden/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/democracy-in-danger-trump-biden/</guid>
      <description>With democracy and pluralism under attack around the world, I interviewed New York Times columnist Roger Cohen and academic and former deputy Knesset speaker Naomi Chazan to delve further into this troubling trend in the United States, Israel and all around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIF event: Interviewing Thomas Friedman</title>
      <link>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/interview-thomas-friedman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/interview-thomas-friedman/</guid>
      <description>This week I interviewed New York Times columnist Thomas Friedman about the US election, the Trump presidency and the Middle East.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIF event: Interviewing Kevin Rudd</title>
      <link>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/interview-kevin-rudd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/interview-kevin-rudd/</guid>
      <description>As a former prime minister and foreign minister, there are few people with a better understanding of Australia’s role in the world and our history with the Israeli-Palestinian conflict than Kevin Rudd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIF event: In conversation with Martin Indyk</title>
      <link>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/interview-martin-indyk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/interview-martin-indyk/</guid>
      <description>With Prime Minister Netanyahu actively advancing plans to annex parts of the West Bank and President Trump pushing his own plan for the Middle East, I interviewed former US ambassador to Israel and former US special envoy for Israeli-Palestinian negotiations – not to mention NIF Australia’s co-patron!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
