<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Australia on Liam Getreu</title>
    <link>https://liamgetreu.com/tags/australia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Australia on Liam Getreu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-au</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://liamgetreu.com/tags/australia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Haaretz op-ed: &#39;How Australia’s New Leaders Really See Israel and the Palestinians&#39;</title>
      <link>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/labor-government-israel-palestine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/labor-government-israel-palestine/</guid>
      <description>Following Labor&amp;rsquo;s federal election win, I wrote this op-ed for Israeli newspaper Haaretz on what it means for the Australia-Israel relationship:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIF event: Ohad Naharin on BDS, Israel-Palestine and the Sydney Festival</title>
      <link>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/interview-ohad-naharin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/interview-ohad-naharin/</guid>
      <description>Over the last month, calls to boycott the Sydney Festival after it received sponsorship from the Israeli embassy for a production of Naharin’s Decadance have featured prominently on social and mainstream media.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sydney Morning Herald op-ed: &#39;Sydney Festival boycott a blunt instrument that blocks voices of dissent&#39;</title>
      <link>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/sydney-festival-boycott/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/sydney-festival-boycott/</guid>
      <description>Following pressure on the Sydney Festival to reject funding from the Israeli embassy to host Ohad Naharin and the Batsheva Dance Company&amp;rsquo;s Decadance, I wrote this op-ed for the Sydney Morning Herald:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIF event: In conversation with Senator Penny Wong</title>
      <link>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/penny-wong-10-years/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/penny-wong-10-years/</guid>
      <description>For the event celebrating 10 years since the New Israel Fund&amp;rsquo;s establishment in Australia we hosted a number of speakers, including a conversation with Senator the Hon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIF event: Foreign Correspondents Speak Out</title>
      <link>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/foreign-correspondents-nif-event/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/foreign-correspondents-nif-event/</guid>
      <description>For this NIF event, I moderated a discussion with John Lyons, the author of a new book, Dateline Jerusalem which looks at how Israel is covered by the Australian media and a former Middle East Correspondent for the Australian, Anshel Pfeffer senior correspondent and columnist for Haaretz and the Israeli correspondent for the Economist and Dina Kraft, a Tel Aviv-based journalist for the Los Angeles Times and Christian Science Monitor, to hear how foreign correspondents work to tell other people’s stories and shape the discourse in their home country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIF event: Adam Bandt and Tamar Zandberg on progressive politics</title>
      <link>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/adam-bandt-tamar-zandberg/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/adam-bandt-tamar-zandberg/</guid>
      <description>I had the privilege to interview two leaders shaping their country&amp;rsquo;s political conversations – Adam Bandt, leader of the Australian Greens, and Tamar Zandberg, Knesset member and former leader of Israel’s Meretz – on how they are shifting the political goal posts and taking decisive action rooted in shared values of equality, democracy and justice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Labor’s resolution ‘doesn’t undermine support for Israel’</title>
      <link>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/alp-occupation-resolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/alp-occupation-resolution/</guid>
      <description>The Australian Jewish News published my op-ed on resolutions about Israel-Palestine at Labor&amp;rsquo;s recent national conference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NIF event: Interviewing Kevin Rudd</title>
      <link>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/interview-kevin-rudd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/interview-kevin-rudd/</guid>
      <description>As a former prime minister and foreign minister, there are few people with a better understanding of Australia’s role in the world and our history with the Israeli-Palestinian conflict than Kevin Rudd.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On ABC News discussing Israel’s plans for annexation</title>
      <link>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/abc-annexation/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/abc-annexation/</guid>
      <description>I was on ABC The World discussing Israel&amp;rsquo;s plans for annexation and the Australian government&amp;rsquo;s response.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the Australian government’s decision to recognise West Jerusalem</title>
      <link>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/australia-jerusalem-embassy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://liamgetreu.com/posts/australia-jerusalem-embassy/</guid>
      <description>I was interviewed for AM in gauging reactions from the Jewish and Palestinian communities on the Australian government&amp;rsquo;s announcement regarding West Jerusalem.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
